prop eight Section 8 are we
ready let's
roast
guy you look like a Jeff Ross bean bag
[Applause]
[Music]
chair tomor you're so hot but you're so
ghetto and uneducated I never know
whether I should you or try to
teach you Shakespeare through hip
hop God you too fat to be trying to ride
dick my
this so gay he only came out
the closet so his daddy would spank
[Applause]
him Jamar at least my father waited for
me to come out of the closet to reject
me
um Jamar Jamar grew up poor but his mom
did the best with what she had
unfortunately what she had was crack
cocaine he is very very lucky that you
cannot pay for an abortion with an EBT
card guy you look like a malignant well
tumor that's topical it's a sad shame
you got all that blood and can't donate
none of
it thank you
w jamar's never met his dad which makes
a lot of sense women rarely keep in
touch with the guy who paid them two
baloney sandwiches to behind a
dumpster that's it that's going to do it
God brandom to more
neighbors I'm all up for presentation
and this uh when they came out with the
fans I'm like how's he going to top that
and then he brought his
[Music]
[Applause]
neighborhood
thank you wave you did great guy but I
gotta give it to Jamar in his
neighborhood I thought when you first
came out that it was over I didn't
realiz you was going up against Jamal
I've seen Jamal before he's very very
risky and
um I've seen before I was actually
scared and then um The Comebacks was
amazing I got to go with guy
okay uh
oh that's the first time black guys ever
voted for a gay person all right deah
you both seemed very confident I I think
personally it's tough but I got to go
with Jamar I mean that bean bag
chair
joke it all comes down to you Jeffrey
who do you like as always guy your jokes
are so so well written the shakespear
through hip-hop jokes so funny that was
a good one yeah you're really becoming
just a great comic and super funny guy
however I think we all know tonight was
jamar's night you killed it
buddy
love
damn
hey my mama watching this he was
fantastic I was afraid I'm not
going to lie oh a gay guy didn't win
when it was an all straight guy judging
panel surprise
surprise yeah I feel no he had a
stronger night give me a kiss all right
man my mama watching this mama I swear
to
[Music]
God B